Dancing in the streets, rolling on your
feet. Dancing by that.
Dancing in the street. Dance a little
beat all over
the street.
I'm looking for the sound of emotion
making dreams of my life. I was feeling
no satisfaction till I hear this music
right now. With me happy and free to
feel you all right. Let the music play.
And every day the rhythm go. Keep on
dancing in the streets. Dancing to the
beat.
Dancing in the streets. Dancing to the
beat. Dancing on your feet.
Dancing in the street. Rolling on your
feet. Dancing.
Dancing. Dancing in the street. Dancing
on the street.
It is a la.
>> You see Trixie told you she'd be deep
sparkle. Turn your back on that girl for
five seconds and she ends up in the club
shaking her gill up for bits.
>> On God, she do throw it back though. Not
going to lie.
>> All right. All right. Settle down. You
loser animals can't even afford an
encore.
>> Oh,
ass off the stage now.
What the hell was that?
>> No. What the hell was that performance?
So, I was dancing. So, what? It's not
like any pony touched me. Now, before
you lecture me, check this out.
See this? This is called cash. Ponies
throw it at you when you're hot and
talented. Are you jealous?
Remove that dirty money from the great
and powerful Trixiey's majestic face at
once. You think those ponies in that
club were watching because they think
you're talented? They were looking at
you like an object of their lustful
desires and nothing more.
>> Oh no. Adults at a nightclub thinking
dirty thoughts. What a tragedy. That's
not what I'm saying. You deserve better
than that. You don't understand that
world.
>> And you do.
>> Trixie isn't going to talk about this
right now. It's raining and she's cold.
Trixie is going back to the car. Sparkle
beat her up. I wish she would stop
talking in third person and using just
the second half of my name because for a
second I didn't know what she said.
>> So you're just storming off now? That's
real mature. She shouldn't have slapped
you. Yeah, no [__] But she only did it
because she cares. Trixie spent years
performing for crowds that didn't really
care about her. And she's seen
performers get destroyed by that life.
Oh, please. I'm not going to crumble
because some drunk dude tossed me 10
bits. I know, but at least see it from
her perspective and think about what
that money really stands for.
Oh, for the love of
Why did you make me go and do that? Do
what? You mean the dancing? I didn't
make you do anything. We both did
because we're one and the same. Well, it
won't happen again because I'm done
being dragged around by your bad
decisions.
>> Mine? You were the one grinding on a
pole 5 minutes ago and you loved it.
Now, let me just
You've got to be fisting me. You spent
too much time with them. They've been
teaching you all this stupid be a better
pony tom foolery and now you're
practically your own pony. And if you're
your own pony, then I can't go back
inside unless you will it. GG. Get
wrecked, nerd.
>> That tea sounds like piss. That's really
sexy. Thank you. Would you like some
sugar? No. Trixie and Flawless, I'm
afraid the two of you are going to have
to stay with me in Canterlock Castle for
the time being. What for? As you know,
the national showare mascot has forbid
you from using magic. And with Trixie
Bell's inevitable return, my sister
insists that you are to be under strict
surveillance as she believes you may be
the reincarnation of the long dead star
catcher who he really hates.
What about me?
>> Celestia doesn't want to talk to you.
She feels that since you started a
family, you haven't been giving her as
much attention lately. Are you for real,
skis? What a load of rubbish. What is
she a puppy?
Haha. It's funny because ponies aren't
legally allowed to wear clothes because
I made it illegal so I can spank them on
the ass.
Princess Celestia, I can see that you
answered the call.
>> You are actively choosing to sit there
and not speak. Why are you like this? Oh
my god, the silent treatment. You white
[__] are all the same. You're not
better than me just because you're
white, you know. You're not. God. God
damn it. You're not.
Sister, unmute thyself. Thou are looking
ridiculous.
>> Oh my Celestia, I cannot believe you are
doing this. Are you a baby? A little
wittle baby?
>> Sister, thou are indeed behaving like a
poopy baby. Answer your student.
>> She just farted into the phone. Ask her
if Queen Chrysalis can come to my
sleepover.
>> Luna wants to know if Queen Chrysalis
can come over.
>> No, she's evil.
>> $1 million, sweetie Bell. $1 million6.
That's how much this room costs.
We finally made it to the top. And to
think all we had to do was ask Rainbow
Dash to simply give us a small loan of a
million dollars.
>> Okay, this room kind of a vibe. It's a
little ominous and it's giving back
rooms just a tad, but I'm not mad at it.
So, does this make me a millionaire,
too? Because you always say that your
successes are my successes also.
>> Only when those successes don't equate
to financial gain, darling.
>> That's not fair, Rarity. You take from
my piggy bank all the time.
>> Yeah. And I also say you can have your
own opinions. And if you don't agree
with mine, that's okay because every
pony is born different. So, no pony has
to feel personally attacked. And if they
don't agree with me, that's fine. But I
do want you to know that I am personally
attacking you this time, sweetie Bell.
If you think we're sharing this
million-dollar penthouse 50/50 like it's
a Kit Kat bar, you might as well unal
alive yourself right now.
>> I'm telling mommy and daddy you bucked
me.
>> Go ahead. I'll buck them too, [__]
There are no witnesses up in here. All
right. So, I can throw you out this
window. So, don't you catch an attitude
with me, little girl. I'm ready to go to
jail tonight. Now, let me see if Rainbow
Dash is on her way.
You on your way?
>> Yeah, almost there.
>> Sweetie Bell, her text bubbles. They're
green. Rainbow Dash, why are your
messages green?
>> What do you mean?
>> It means you have an Android.
>> Yeah, it's sick.
>> Oh my god, bro.
>> Oh, hell no, man. WHAT THE [__]
WHY WOULD YOU CHOOSE GREEN BUBBLES?
>> I didn't choose it. That's just how it
is.
>> Don't come over.
>> I'm already in the elevator.
>> You have got to be pooping on my butt
right now. I am standing in a $1 million
apartment and Rainbow Dash is texting me
from a device that produces green
bubbles.
>> Rarity, are you and Rainbow Dash dating?
>> Disgusting. Why the hell would you ask
something so homosexual?
>> I'm only asking because the only reason
we're in this penthouse is because you
borrowed $1 million from Rainbow Dash
and she only did it because she
obviously likes you. Isn't it mean to
string her along?
>> Rainbow Dash is perfectly aware of what
she's doing, sweetie Bell. And I'm sure
it is a platonic loan.
Oh, hello Rainbow. I didn't expect the
rest of you bad [__] Haha. Welcome
to Rarity's brand new penthouse. Bought
and paid for by my gal pal, Rainbow
Dash. Have a seat and relax in the lap
of luxury.
>> Ignore them. I only brought them, so you
can't run.
>> What would I have to run from? And how
did you get a tractor in the building?
>> Huh? You're worried about that? I'd be
more worried about myself if I was you,
Gal?
>> Why are you surrounding me?
>> Oh, we're just standing around.
>> So, Rarity, about that little loan I
gave you. the million dollars.
>> Yeah, that Well, long story short, I
want it back.
>> Why?
>> Because if I gave you a million dollars,
I lowkey thought you would offer to like
sit on my face or something, but like
only as a prank. It's not like I want
you to sit on my face and drop a
streaming hot dookie right into my
mouth.
>> That sounds pretty gay. Girls shouldn't
poopy in girls mouths. There is also the
fact that feces are not meant to be
dropped in another's mouth for it could
lead to serious medical issues.
>> But mostly because it's gay.
>> Rainbow Dash, I don't understand. I
thought you gave me a million dollars
for free. I don't do that stuff. Give me
my money.
>> Haha, that's funny, [__] It's almost
like you can't pay Dashy back even
though that was all of the money in her
bank account.
>> Wait, all of it? Rainbow. That is deeply
irresponsible. You should never allocate
100% of your liquid assets into a single
unsecured personal loan.
>> Y'all may be kicked up in the back seat,
but y'all some crazy ass mofos. No cap.
Now get out of my way. I'm Audi 5,000.
Don't you freaking touch me. I'm whiter
than you. I have more rights.
>> Where the [__] is my money, Rarity?
Return to me the money of the Rainbow
Clan, you dirty skank.
>> I don't have your money. Get out of my
penthouse.
>> Somehow do something before she kills my
big sister. It was too dangerous to let
us and a million dollars.
Damn. Rainbow Dash sure got some fat
butt cheeks.
I spot you a millie. And this is how you
repay me, [__]
[__] it's out of gas.
Wait, farts can technically be used for
energy because they contain flammable
gases like methane and hydrogen.
It worked.
Rainbow Dash, stop. You're going to kill
her.
>> Am I the only one wondering how Rainbow
Dash got a million dollars to give away?
>> How is that weird? Her family owns the
copyrights to every color in the
rainbow. Wait, really? Why is this the
first time I'm hearing about this?
>> That's not the kind of stuff we want to
talk with you about, Fluttershy. Because
the minute one of us show an ounce of
success, you're always the first one to
try and take advantage of us. We all
hate you for it.
>> No, I don't. No. No. Actually, you know
what? You're right. I do take from you
girls, but that's because we are friends
and friends share things like money.
>> Oh, no, Fluttershy. You don't share. You
just take.
>> Yeah. Thanks for proving our point.
>> Rainbow Dash, I found you. Oh, hi, Scoo.
>> Oh my god. Look, she's blushing.
>> I am not. I'm just saying hi to my
friend. Sweetie Belle, why the [__] are
you acting so queer? You best not still
be on that gay [__] for real skis. Well,
um, actually, I was wondering if maybe
you wanted to hang out. McDonald's has
this new thing called the K-pop Demon
Hunters Neil, and I heard it's um,
really K-poppy, and I thought maybe we
could, you know, try it together since
me and Rarity are rich now.
>> Y, these Phillies need Jesus.
Look, Scoots, I got roomie. I don't know
who that is.
By the way, how are you liking that big
arch scootalo? It's really sending.
Yeah, I don't think I would be able to
finish if I got one. So, I just got a
normal cheeseburger, which is still too
big. Haha. Hey, Scoots. When I asked you
out, I thought you were going to say no.
Oh, really? Why is that? Because you're
so much cooler than me. I mean, come on.
You skateboard without a helmet. And
your mane isn't this fluffy ball of
cotton candy like mine is. And you don't
care about how you smell like crap,
which is the textbook definition of cool
when you put it that way. Yeah, I guess
I am kind of a badass, sweetie Belle,
but you've got cool stuff about you,
too. What else is badass about me?
You're really good at uh that thing.
What thing? Scoots, please be honest
with me. Are you just giving me a pity
date because I'm a nerd? What? No way.
Because that would be extremely messed
up, sweetie. In fact, there's actually
something I've been wanting to say for a
while now. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. This
is it. She's going to confess to me.
Holy guacamole.
April fools.
Hold on. Don't move.
Oh my god. [__] You should totally see
the look on your face right now. The
whole school's going to lose it tomorrow
when they peep this. Oh, be a good
sport, [__] ass. I know. Even you got
to think this is [__] hilarious.
That's right. Today is April Fool's Day,
huh? You're not laughing. It's funny.
This whole thing is
um Sweetie Bell, I won't post this to
the cloud if you don't want me to. No,
do it. Upload it. Obviously, I'm a joke
to you anyway, so you might as well let
everyone else join in and laugh at the
[__] ass clown.
Okay, big dog. I'm going out back to
smoke a cigarette and play Call of Duty
Black Ops with Rainbow Dash.
Sweetie Bell, what happened? Whatever is
the reason for your tears.
>> Thanks for inviting me over despite
Celestia's wishes, Luna. I knew at least
one of the princesses were a real one.
>> It's weird how you can reach this window
despite how high we are.
>> It's not weird. I'm standing on my hind
legs.
>> It's still pretty weird.
>> For the record, it's not because I want
her here. Our therapist shoves mandatory
playdates on us. One sec. I got to take
my pills.
>> Oh, right.
>> Yeah, same.
>> It's Friday, right?
Trixie, I don't want to be in Luna's
house no more. You promised to take me
to see Scream 7 tonight.
>> Trixie made that promise long before the
score was put up on Rotten Tomatoes, you
[__] Trixie refuses to feed into the
Hollywood machine that rewards cheap
cash grabs by weaponizing nostalgia.
>> You bought three Minecraft popcorn
buckets. Four. The fourth one has yet to
be delivered and they don't count
because these are investments. They're
going to be worth a lot of money when
Jack Black dies. But but I already told
my friends I was seeing it. If I show up
to school without having watched it.
>> Oh, please. What's the worst that could
possibly happen?
>> I go to school on Monday and some pony
asks what I thought about the movie and
I'll have to admit I didn't see it and
suddenly I'm the girl in class who
didn't see Scream 7 because her
overprotective mommy wouldn't let her.
I'll lose what little social standing I
currently have. My motivation and grades
start to slip and then I drop out to
flip burgers. Where my co-workers in 10
years talk about their fond elementary
school memories about seeing Scream 7
and I can't join in there either because
I was locked up in Princess Luna's
bedroom on a Friday night. Then I'll
head home after my 8-hour shift to my
cheap ass apartment with thin walls. You
have given this an alarming amount of
thought. Flawless sparkle moon. As the
princess of the moon and the word moon
being in your name, I am your superior
and I forbid you from climbing out that
window.
>> You are not my superior. You're gay.
>> I am so too in every way.
>> Oh yeah. Can you do this?
>> What? You didn't do anything.
>> Nice debate, [__]
>> Okay, the industry wins tonight. We
shall watch Scream 7.
>> Thanks, Mom.
Hey, look over there. Isn't that Uncle
Shining Armor?
Oh, thank you so much for taking me out
tonight, Shiny. You're always such a
doll.
Oh my, I'm quite gassy. Perhaps we
shouldn't have stopped by Taco Bell. For
those beefy potato burritos, haha, I'm
quite the stinky princess.
My goodness, it's quite rank, isn't it,
dear? If I fart during the movie, you
might have to drag me back out to the
car and punish me for stinking up the
theater.
What a woman.
I just don't get why you're such a dumb
baby sometimes, Mary. Last week, you got
off to skinning a man alive with nothing
but a toothbrush and posting it on the
dark web. It's different when I do it.
I'm sorry I'm ruining the movie for you.
We probably missed a good 10 minutes by
now.
>> It's okay. I'm just happy to be here
with you cuz you're so cute. You're like
the living embodiment of everything good
God wished for when she made the world.
What? You never heard of spontaneous
pony liquefification on the dark web? I
guess you can't expect much from a
normie. I bet you've never even seen a
single gore video in your entire life.
[__] All this homicidal talk has got me
hot and bothered. And it's not even 3:00
in the morning. There's police outside.
That wouldn't happen to be about the
body you dumped in the woods, would it?
>> Oh, yeah. That's probably it.
>> You said you handled it.
>> I did, but then the blood started doing
this weird bubbling thing and it popped
everywhere and it got gross. So, I kind
of halfassed it. You're such an idiot
sometimes.
What the hell? You botched a murder. At
least hold my hoof. Make it look real.
>> Dude, I get it. But like this is a
public place. That's the point, dumbass.
An officer will be less willing to come
up to you if they believe you are on an
intimate date. Especially if they lack
real probable cause to confront you.
Your hoof is all sweaty. Relax. You
don't need to be so nervous. Oh, shut up
or I'm breaking up with you again.
Oh my god. I'm going to ask a question,
baby girl. And I want you to know this
is a safe judgment free zone. That
sentence has never once led to safety
with you.
>> Dude, are you wearing a freaking thong
right now? Okay. Yeah, but in my
defense, we are going to the bar after
the movie. And I made a tactical
assumption that perhaps later there
might be marrynt and possibly smooching
and maybe something more intimate. And I
wanted to catch you off guard with
something exciting. It's okay. They're
cute and you look really good in them.
And they'll probably look even better
when I'm taking them off you later.
I really need to buy some WD40 for that
door. Well, baby, are you ready? I know
how long you've been waiting for this.
>> Just start the show already, mama, but
close the door first.
Speechless, are you? Well, there isn't
really much to talk about, honestly. You
kind of look like a light bulb.
I'm embarrassed.
Starcatcher, I've been hunting your
sorry ass for over a thousand years now,
but never in my wildest dreams would I
have expected you to be reborn as a
showare like Trixie. I almost pity you.
It makes me think leaving you like this
would be a more deserving fate. You dumb
queer. You disgusting homosexual [__]
I'm homophobic. In fact, I'm so
homophobic that I have sex with men all
the time just to show they don't turn me
on. They can't call you gay if you do it
to prove a point. Hey, Mom. Want to hear
a joke?
>> No, I just want to watch the movie.
>> Something doesn't feel right. Maybe we
shouldn't have left the sanctity of
Canterlock Castle.
>> That really took me by surprise. I
almost dookieed myself.
>> You did dookie yourself. I can smell it.
>> That will be $39.99.
>> The great and powerful Trixie does not
receive that much money from her wife in
the weekly allowance. She will offer you
$4 and some change if you cut it in half
and give her the top half. actually the
bottom half because Trixie still want to
eat popcorn out of it before adding it
to her collection of major blockbuster
themed popcorn buckets. We don't do
business like that.
>> Then what does Trixie do with these $4?
It's not even enough to buy half a big
arch from McDonald's.
>> I don't know why you're asking me.
>> That was a rhetorical question. Trixie
is just venting because she doesn't have
a job.
>> Trixie, where are you going? We're
supposed to stay with Princess Luna for
protection. If the great and powerful
Trixie can't watch Scream 7, then she's
at least going to purchase a limited
edition Scream 7 popcorn bucket to put
on the shelf back home next to her
Freddy Fazbear and Minecraft creeper
that looks like a penis.
>> Ah, hell no. Trixie got pulled down into
Synth Wave City.
>> Trixie, hold on.
That's him, huh? Trixie Bell, the cult
gesture. He doesn't look like all that
much to me. Trixie doesn't even need an
alicorn's protection. Trixie will take
him down all on her own.
>> Impossible. She deflected a child's
bouncy ball traveling at 12 miles per
hour.
>> The great and powerful Trixie has been
attending Community Center martial arts
classes. A yellow belt in karate, but
that typically takes 3 to 6 months of
consistent training. Ponies don't
normally have the attention span for
that.
I see. I guess I might have
underestimated you a bit.
>> Yeah, you did, [__] Now the great and
powerful Trixie is going to you. Thanks,
Celestia. He doesn't realize that Trixie
just pissed on a really long sock.
>> I'll fight alongside you, mother. Don't
forget I enrolled in those Wednesday to
Friday afternoon classes, too.
>> You literally just signed up 2 days ago.
How do you already have a brown belt?
Get back here.
>> Fist me. Her legs are longer than mine,
so she's faster than me. I have to lose
her by cutting through this alleyway.
>> Flawless. The ginger Latino is trying to
make a break for it. Cut him off through
the bathrooms.
I was drinking that.
>> This is kind of fun, huh? Sweetie Bell.
It's kind of like we're camping. If you
ignore that fact that we got mugged
three times in the past 15 minutes,
>> I miss my bed. You're supposed to be
responsible for me, Rarity. Mom and dad
trusted you to take care of me, but my
life sucks. Big fat hairy balls. I wish
I was living with them instead. At least
then I would have a pillow to cry into.
>> Oh, sweetie Bell.
>> Rarity, I'm sorry.
>> Damn, she looks kind of like a Twinkie.
Twinky. Twinky Bell. Haha, I am so
funny. I'm just like Pinkie Pie in the
head and no one even knows it.
>> No, you're right. I'm a failure as a big
sister. But you're an even failure as a
little sister and as a pony in general.
So, we are perfectly balanced. At least
we aren't background ponies. We have
feelings too, you know.
>> You're lucky you're a unicorn and not a
Pegasus because I would have called you
a slur by now, you repulsive secondass
horse.
>> I'm just mad about what happened at
McDonald's. Scoo and me ate big arches.
But she April fooled me and took a
picture of me crying and said she'd post
it so everyone could laugh at me.
Okay, now this is just bananas. You
actually set up camp on the sidewalk.
Damn, I thought you'd at least crash at
Twilight's house or some [__] but this
is just sad.
>> Hobie looking like a Twinkie. Shut up,
Scoo. Why don't you make yourself useful
for once and ask your precious Rainbow
Dash to stop stealing houses from the
needy? Shut up.
>> Damn, Squirt, you really told that white
[__] off. Give your sister some skin.
>> Oh yeah. Well, at least me and Rarity
are actually real sisters, not some fake
pretenders like you. You fat smelly
meanie. What the hell did you just say?
Don't make me get out of this banana
bite. Rainbow Dash isn't even related to
you. Actually, I take that back. Maybe
you really are sisters after all because
you're just a couple of lousy tryhards
who think bullying ponies is a cool
thing to do when it isn't. It just makes
ponies hate you.
>> Hey, I'm sorry. I was just like poking
fun and [__]
>> I know, Rainbow.
>> Why are you apologizing to the enemy?
>> Because there's a difference between
trash talk and straight up bullying you,
dweeb. I was messing with Rarity and I
was going to give her her house back
tomorrow because we do this kind of [__]
for funsies because we're friends. But I
would never do anything that would truly
nuke her life. And seriously, if you
really took a picture of Sweetie Bell
without her consent, that is beyond
shitty, especially because she's ugly as
[__] sin and not a sexy piece of hot
ass like me. So, you got to delete that
right now.
>> Don't even bother because I don't care
anymore anyway. This friendship is
officially over.
Well, kid, it's been fun lapping around
the neighborhood on these banana bikes,
but I got to head home.
>> You're not taking me with you?
>> Why would I do that? You're not even my
sister.
Apple Bloom, what are you doing here? I
was using the poop bucket. Do you want
to help me wash it? No. Apple Bloom, be
honest. Am I a bully? Yeah, but it's
fine because no pony expects anything
else since you don't have any parents
and you're a crippled Pegasus who can't
fly and you're an [__] You were
supposed to lie to me.
>> Sweetie, what is it?
>> I I don't know, but I'm getting a
headache for some reason.
Oh my Celestia.
I am not a bully and I will kill you for
saying that.
>> You will burn Apple Bloom along with the
rest of your inbredad family. Take it up
the ass, [__]
>> Holy Jesus.
>> She has wings, but she is a disabled
Pegasus bound to the ground like an
Earth pony. Yet she flies. That green
eye of hers belongs to Sweetie Belle,
and it grants her access to an infinite
amount of unicorn magic. She is a
fractured trinity. Scootaloo is no
longer powerful. She is the closest
thing to a god this world has ever
produced.
Twilight Scuttaloo has become God. And
because her name is Scooaloo, she's
awakened a new ability that initiates
the motion she chooses like a scooter.
Be it physical, conceptual, or even
metaphorical. For example, if Scoodilis
starts thinking about wanting a pony
dead, the concept of that pony living
against her is erased from existence,
and they automatically die. The only
rational course we all have now is to
bow to our new overlord and pray that
that literal baby does not destroy us
all. Twilight, only you and the rest of
the main six can save the world from
that literal baby. If not, it's GG.
Bubba.
>> Rainbow, get on it.
>> No way. I'm not going up there to chat
with that demonic little psycho.
>> Look out. Squirtle is hiding behind that
rock with a gun.
>> As the leader of the Rainbow Dash fan
club, I demand that you leave my sister
alone.
>> Every pony, get behind me. I'll protect
every single one of us.
It worked. Every pony follow me. We'll
be safe inside Pinkie Pie's house.
Good thinking, Rarity. By saying we were
going to Pinkiey's house, we were able
to hide in your house safely. Oh no,
she's going to kill Pinkie Pie.
>> Okay, Phillies. Today, Auntie Pinky is
going to show you how to make hot world
famous pot of baked beans.
Pinkie Pie just got stabbed. I'm heading
out there to save her. No, Rainbow Dash.
Don't be a hero.
>> Scootaloo has seven IQ points total. So,
if you just rush and it might take
Scutalo about 20 seconds to register
that you're Rainbow Dash and not a
different Blue Pony, that's more than
enough time for her to slit your throat
with a knife. And you are purposefully
ignoring that blatant fact simply
because Pinkie Pie has the highest
likelihood of letting you smash. You
will die a virgin.
>> Sputal look found an open window. It's
every pony for themselves.
>> Oh my god, her eyes.
>> Don't worry, she still has one more.
>> Blast that [__] Flutterbutt.
Twilight. The stinky gusts of
Fluttershy's fart is so powerful that
it's pushing the planet towards the sun.
Fluttershy, stop it. You're going to
destroy the world.
Fluttershy, I'm afraid you have left me
with no other choice. Forgive me,
Princess Celestia, for never would I
have dreamed I would be forced to use
such a technique against a valuable
friend like Fluttershy.
>> That's Twilight Sparkle's evolved form.
The scorching twilight, a form that was
taught to her directly by Princess
Celestia herself.
>> Fluttershy, I'm afraid you have left me
with no other choice.
Scorching Twilight strength wasn't
enough, so she's using her recently
acquired dragon powers to rely on
strength rather than speed.
>> Fluttershy, I'm afraid you have left me
with no other choice.
Scorching twilight of the abyssal white
flame. A form which eclipses even that
of the olicorn. All this time I thought
it was only a myth. What the hell do you
think you're doing sticks? You are truly
fools and you shall suffer the same face
as a look if you challenge my ass.
>> Where is Scuta going now? Miss Cheerly's
house is that way. Damn, she's fast as
[__] She's got to be moving at like 9
mph.
There's only one spell that I know of
that can stop Scodaloo now. I don't
remember the incantation for it.
>> I think I know which one you're talking
about. Isn't it that one forbidden spell
that shuts off the access to magic for
disabled people?
>> Yeah, that's it. But around 67% of
ponies are mentally disabled by default
and [__] So, it was deemed too deadly
for Equestria. So, Princess Celestia put
it in a glass barrier next to the Burger
King. And the barrier is so powerful
that no pony can break it.
>> Then, how do we get it out?
>> It's simple, you dumb bimbo. We ask
someone with fingers who isn't a pony to
get it out for us. Let's go, Rainbow
Dash.
>> How's it going, [__]
>> Oh my goodness. Is Gojo from Jiu-Jitsu
Kase. Gojo, please feed me a carrot for
I am but a tiny little horse in your
holy presence.
>> Me, too.
>> You can leave that glass barrier to me,
Twilight Sparkle. In fact, I don't even
got to use my domain expansion
abilities. If I twerk next to that glass
dome with my fat booty cheeks, the earth
shaking claps of my ass will be so loud
that the sound waves created by the huge
sonic booms will destroy that barrier as
easy as if it was wet cardboard.
the
>> Oh
>> yeah, it's just as I thought. This [__]
is bulletproof glass. It's no wonder why
a horse couldn't break it. But I ain't
no horse.
>> Sweet Celestia, check out the turd
cutter on that man.
>> It's working. Keep throwing it back.
Gojo is throwing it back so hard the
planet itself is being violently shaken.
>> It's a necessary evil. Keep going, Gojo.
It worked. Gojo. You saved us.
>> Well, I'm going back home to take a huge
[__] Oh, but before I go, Rarity, I
just got to say for a horse, you are one
damn fine, sexy mama.
>> Let's get this book to Scootaloo and
read the spell.
>> You gave me an F in math class
yesterday.
>> Scootaloo, you haven't come to class for
3 weeks.
>> Get away from the 53-year-old underpaid
elementary school teacher.
>> Now, this doesn't have to get ugly,
darling. If you stand down without a
fight, we won't have to use this spell
book that is capable of taking away the
magic from all disabled ponies
worldwide.
Okay, that did not go how I expected.
>> Damn it, Rarity. Thank god I ripped the
very page we need with the spell and
stuffed it between my fat butt cheeks.
[__] This forbidden spell specifically
doesn't work on Scuttaloo.
Why are you doing this to us?
>> Because it's not fair for others to have
a mommy and daddy and sister when I
don't and I don't have friends.
>> I'm your friend Scootaloo.
>> You are
>> April fools.
>> I'm your friend Scootaloo.
>> Prove it then. What's my name?
>> [__] I don't know if this one is Apple
Bloom or Sweetie Bell, but I know it
specifically has to be one of those two.
It can't be Scooaloo because Scootaloo
is the white one.
What the is this? Just stuffing.
That body is a fake. The real Trixie
Bell is right there.
No, wait. I don't taste very good.
Star Catcher. Star Catcher, help me. I
don't want to die.
Does it hurt?
It's fine.
It's not fine. He hit you.
>> Well, he won't do it again.
>> And what makes you so sure?
>> Because you'll stop him again for me,
just like you always do.
I'm not always going to be around to
fight your battles for you, Belle. One
of these days, you're going to have to
learn to stick up for yourself.
Ponies wouldn't have to fight at all if
I were the one in charge of things.
What?
>> If I were in charge, there wouldn't be
bullies and guys like me wouldn't get
picked on for being different.
>> And how would you manage that exactly?
>> Hurt someone weaker than you, you die.
That sounds awfully strict. If something
keeps ponies safe, then it doesn't
matter if it's strict or not.
>> The world is already messy because every
pony thinks they know what's right.
>> Then what about you, Starcatcher? What
do you think?
>> I think sometimes ponies hurt others
because they're the ones really hurting
inside.
So, we're supposed to feel sorry for our
bullies.
>> No, but maybe understand them.
>> Understanding won't stop them from
laughing at my ears.
That's true. They are abnormally large.
But you aren't a normal boy, are you?
Just like how I'm known ordinary girl.
Personally, I find your ears quite cute.
>> You're making fun of me.
Look, a shooting star. Better make a
wish. I don't need to wish on a star
because I already know what I want. And
I know I'll never get it. And what's
that? A world where ponies don't need
wishes to be happy.
>> Oh, Belle.
Hey, let go of me. Nope. This is what
you get for plotting world's domination.
You know, if you ever did run things,
you'd need someone beside you to keep
you from becoming a grumpy old tyrant. I
would not be grumpy.
>> You absolutely would. I just don't like
being scared all the time.
Whatever storms may gather around,
whatever the world throws at you, for as
long as I walk this earth, I promise I
will always protect you.
>> You aren't a normal.
>> Oh, well, I find them cute.
>> I promise I will always protect you.
You saved me.
>> Who are you really? Why do you have
Princess Trixie Bell's name?
>> My name? Oh, right about that. Before I
was who I am now. I was a I was an
alicorn princess.
>> Of course you were.
>> No, really. I'm serious. I was the
alicorn princess of tricks. But Princess
Trixie Bell vanished a long time ago.
>> Yeah, she did. Being a princess was so
lonely, and she wanted to feel what it's
like to be ordinary one day. I don't
remember exactly what happened, but she
did this forbidden spell and forcefully
ripped the alicorn magic out of herself.
When she did, most of her was destroyed.
It was like she unraveled the strings
that held her together, and the next
second, the princess of tricks was gone.
and I was left standing in the spot
where she stood. The first clear memory
I have is waking up in a some circus
caravan on the side of the road.
The clowns there weren't kind to me at
all, but they kept me because I could
still make spark from my horn, it was
just enough to entertain. But when the
spark stopped being impressive, they
would resort to cruel acts of torture as
punishment.
>> Okay, I don't really care.
>> I was small. There wasn't anything I
could do except run away. That's when I
met this orphan girl, Skywishes, in the
woods, and it was love at first sight.
That was my first happy memory. Then
Starcatcher showed up. That dumb sparkly
space Pegasus.
It's ironic, huh? I used to be shiny and
powerful. I tore myself apart to be
normal. And who does Skywishes pick?
Starcatcher. Shiny and powerful. That's
why I have to kill you, Trixie. And
Twilight Sparkle, too. You two don't
even realize how much you betrayed me.
>> No, you don't. Sky Wishes is gone. She
lived her life. She made her choice who
to love and it wasn't you.
>> Starcatcher stole Sky Wishes away from
me.
>> You made Starcatcher the villain of your
own story because it was easier than
accepting that Skywishes just didn't
love you back. The ponies of today have
no reason to share blame with ponies of
the past.
Oh boy, more arthritis pills and gay
bacon.
>> Happy birthday.
>> Happy birthday, Sky Wishes. Oh, I
believe the number on your cake is all
wrong.
>> Oh, you're right. It totally is. Hey,
Trixie Bell. Can you go get the correct
candles? If I do a good job, maybe
she'll give me sex. Okay.
>> Trixie Bell, you dummy. You put the six
upside down.
>> You're 39 years old.
>> Actually, 40, but we didn't have a four
and a zero candle.
Starcatcher, do you think I'll ever be
adopted?
>> Well, yesterday I would have said yes.
But now that I know every pony in this
orphanage are actually 40-year-old
miniature horses rather than children,
I'm suddenly inclined to say no. Oh, but
I'm certain there's still a family out
there for you somewhere. One who will
love you even though you are a [__]
with two part-time jobs. I I know it's
against dorm rules for me to butt in,
but if it means anything to you. I I've
always thought it would be neat to have
a sister.
>> Starcatcher, are you saying you want to
adopt me?
>> Oh dear, I must go. It seems some pony
strung Bell up by his ears again.
>> Starcatcher Trixie Bell stole my candy
again. I had it hidden behind the cereal
box and he still found it. I bought that
candy with my own money. Well,
technically it was your money, but you
gave it to me, so that makes it my
money. Star catcher.
Oh, she's in the shower.
You really wear this thing every day?
Yuck. That really stinks.
It's kind of gross.
I wasn't sniffing it.
>> I didn't say you were. But why are you
in my room?
>> Trixie Bell stole my candy. I hide it in
new places every time and he still finds
it. I think he cheats somehow.
Can't you simply buy more tomorrow with
your allowance?
>> I ate it. Well, technically I bought
candy with it and then ate it. You You
look really pretty.
>> That's very kind of you to say.
I I think you're pretty nicel looking
yourself, Skywishes.
>> Your name is pretty, too. Um I really
like stars.
>> My name? That's nice to hear, but I'm
not sure I live up to it anymore. Just
between you and me, I always pictured
myself doing something grand. But
instead, I'm stuck in this place just
cleaning floors. Not that I hate it or
anything like that. I love spending time
with you and Belle, but it isn't what I
pictured for myself when I was small.
>> Cleaning floors is important. If no pony
cleaned floors, every pony would slip
and fall and stuff.
>> I guess that's true. Hey, Skywishes, do
you have a boyfriend?
>> Nope. I don't even know where you get
one.
>> Most people your age are dating someone.
>> Are you making fun of me?
>> I'm sorry. I wasn't trying to make fun
of you. Quite the opposite, in fact.
Actually, a couple years ago, a lady
confessed to me.
It was totally different than when a boy
did it.
Until just recently, I had forgotten
what it felt like. But when I whenever
you're around, I I remember that special
feeling.
I am sorry about that.
I I don't really know what came over me
just then.
>> Great. She runs straight to Starcatcher
the second something happens. I bet
she's telling her about the candy.
>> So, tell me something. What do you want
to do in the future?
>> I want to be a wife.
>> Huh? Are they talking about me?
>> You really just want to be a housewife?
Why not? I think I'm quite the catch.
>> I think you should go to college first.
If the two of us were going to live
together someday, it would be expensive.
>> That's exactly why I should skip college
and get to work immediately.
>> There's a large difference in wages
between ponies who graduate college and
high school.
>> Do we really have to think that far?
>> Then I'll become an architect. Then I
can build a house for us to live in.
Idiot. What was I even thinking?
Of course, you wouldn't be talking about
me.
>> I never intended to do anything.
>> Intent is not the issue. We can't have
you going around playing favorites with
these 40-year-old men and women. Your
relationships with Sky Wishes and Trixie
Bell is honest to God getting weird as
[__] and creepy for some pony that's
just supposed to do laundry and make
food like baked potatoes.
>> I know. I do care about them. What are
they talking about?
>> I don't know.
>> And that is precisely why you cannot
remain. You'll be removed from your
duties immediately and required to
attend a rehabilitation program.
You'll be allowed to return after
completing the course, but you will not
be assigned to the same living unit as
Sky wishes again.
That's fair. Thank you for giving me
another chance.
>> So, it's true they fired you and you
have to leave tonight.
>> Are you just going to keep packing like
I'm not here? You're not supposed to be
in here.
>> Trixie Bell said it was because of me.
Was it because of something I did?
>> No. You did nothing wrong, Skywishes.
>> I don't get it then. Why would you leave
me? You told me I was special, that I
was yours?
>> I shouldn't have done that. But I I I
got lonely and I I wound up prioritizing
you over the others. It's not
appropriate for the position I am in to
form such close friendships with
40-year-old horses that are meant to be
adopted. I'm the one responsible for
where my feelings go. I I'm afraid that
I failed at steering mine properly. I'm
I'm sorry, Skywishes. I am so so sorry.
Belle, what was it exactly you told them
that I had done?
She was a little weird, but she took
care of us, and I forced her out of our
lives, even though she protected me from
bullies and bought us things even when
she wasn't supposed to. How did I forget
that kind of stuff?
>> Unfortunately, love sucks balls and can
make you do some stupid [__] Then what
am I supposed to do?
>> You decide who Starcatcher was, the
monster you painted in your mind or
something different.
>> She was the most radiant pony ever. And
she was the one who won Skywish's
affection. I I think I envied her
because in truth, she was everything I
wanted to be, what I could have been.
>> Not could have been, what you can still
choose to be.
I want to be a pony that protects
others.
>> Who are you?
>> Some pony who isn't meant to exist.
>> I placed a temporary protection spell on
you. You'll be safe now.
>> What about you? That Philly is giving
off a dangerous aura that clouds
everything in despair in a onemile
radius. I have to go or I might end up
being destroyed.
>> Um, thank you for saving me.
>> I think sometimes ponies hurt others
because they're the ones really hurting
inside.
>> That Philly seems pretty sad. Maybe you
should go talk to her.
>> Uh, okay. I will.
>> Starcatcher, you were right. If I want
the world to be better, it has to start
with us. I don't know if I'll stay as
brave or as hopeful as you were. But for
now, I will do my very best to make sure
your will carries on in this future
world because a kindness like yours
can't die with you.
Well, [__] [__] If it isn't Trixie
Bell, how long has it been now? 1,421
years. God damn, how does the time fly?
I remember how that ass of yours was so
nice to slap, like helium filled
balloons. And the sounds you made as I
destroyed your busy, those were real
nice. But if you're looking to go
another round, I must apologize.
I'm afraid you're a tad old for my
preferences now, which are 67 years old.
Wait, is that a sawed off doublebarrel
shotgun? You little [__]
>> It's time to pay for making me take all
four of your inches. Open your mouth so
I can yank out all of your teeth with
rusty pliers.
>> I ain't got no teeth no more. I win,
[__] Now get out of my tent. You're
not in the caravan of cackling horses no
more.
>> You were the only one who was nice to
me.
Thanks for helping me. I'm so lucky
those guys were still alive after 1,421
years.
>> So, what are you going to do now?
>> For the time being, I think I'll travel
around for a bit and see what's changed
in this world.
>> Where, too?
>> There's still a few more clowns out
there from that old circus troop that I
want to hunt down. I think it depends on
them.
>> Well, if you get sick of it, you can
always pay a visit to Ponyville.
>> I try to kill you and you offer me
friendship. That's uncharacteristically
kind for a pony, especially a unicorn.
>> Legends say that you and Starcatcher
were like siblings, right? In a way,
were kind of like family.
>> You know, I'm starting to get why Sky
Wishes was so enthralled by that mare.
If I wasn't so young and naive to the
workings of the heart, maybe our lives
wouldn't have resulted in the tragedy
that it did. I have you to thank for
helping me realize that.
Trixie, let's go already. You promised
me we'd watch Scream 7 tonight.
>> Hi, Scoo.
Sweetie Bell, why are you still here?
Because I want to help you before you
destroy Ponyville.
But why? You hate me. You said Rainbow
Dash isn't my sister and you made fun of
me for it. I only told you that because
you were being a [__] When Apple Bloom
called me a bully, I just lost it. I
realized the two of you weren't really
my friends. And when that happened,
nothing seemed to matter anymore. Your
favorite scooter is your red one, and
your favorite ice cream is Rocky Road,
which we ate together in the back of
Rarity's car during the last Halloween
party at the Ponyville skate park. How
do you remember all that stuff? Because
you told me it. You talk a lot when
you're not trying to look cool and show
off.
I like talking with you, Scoo, and I
love being around you. Even though I'm a
loser with a loser, big sister, you're
not a loser, sweetie Bell. I'm the real
loser. Pretending like I have a big
sister through Rainbow Dash. But she is
your sister. Maybe not through blood,
but something more important.
Friendship.
And friendship is magic.
Sweetie Bell, you reminded us all that
friendship is like magic or some [__]
Because you have saved your small town
of Pony Hill, I bestow upon you one
limitless wish. Name it and it shall be
yours.
>> Well, Scaroo, we could, you know, maybe
continue that date from earlier today.
I'm not gay.
>> Actually, I have reconsidered my
original decision. A unicorn being
romantically entangled with a Pegasus is
not a pairing I can encourage because I
am extraordinarily and proudly racist.
So instead, sweetie Bell, I will give
you a $250 ticket since being gay is
illegal and a second ticket for
attempting to pursue an interracial
relationship, which frankly put I think
is yucky and equivalent to eating a poop
sandwich.
>> Hey sweetie Bell, I'm home.
Tuck yourself in. Dinner is just
finishing up. Luckily, I didn't burn it
this time.
>> What?
>> Nothing. You just uh You look nice.
>> I would have changed, but some pony
decided to finish her race 20 minutes
early. And some pony also insists on
having dinner immediately when she gets
home.
>> It's really not that big of a deal.
Seriously,
>> last time I was 5 minutes late with
dinner, you hovered around the kitchen
like you were starving to death. And
don't laugh, I take this job very
seriously.
>> I know. You're the most talented clown
in Equestria.
>> There are like 12 of us
>> and you're number one.
>> Flattery won't get you out of doing the
dishes. Scoots.
>> Worth a shot.
So, aren't you going to tell me about
it?
>> About what?
>> Oh, don't be like that. You know it's in
all the papers right now. You're the
first pony in history to outfly Rainbow
Dash.
>> Sweetie Bell, can we not talk about
this?
>> And you executed a successful Sonic Rain
Boom.
>> I just want to lay down and sleep before
Rainbow like storms over to beat my ass
or something.
>> It is. You totally smashed Rainbow
Dash's flight record three times over.
>> It wasn't a big deal. You're making it
sound like I beat her. She let me win.
>> In what universe?
>> In in every universe. She's Rainbow
Dash. I can't beat her.
>> Oh, Rainbow Dash. We were just talking
about you.
>> Think you're hot [__] now, Hudweb?
>> Cool it, Rainbow. It was only a race,
>> right? So, you just magically wake up
one day and think, "Hey, I'm going to
beat Rainbow Dash in a race."
>> Well, you are the one who trained me to
go all out?
>> Yeah, but not against me. You know, I
pooped myself. It was wet and it was
itchy. If that didn't happen, I would
have squashed your ass.
>> I don't know. That sounds an awful lot
like an excuse to me. You're getting
real cocky for a pony who used to crash
into mailboxes. And you're getting real
insecure for some pony who says she's
the fastest in Equestria.
Race me now.
>> Scootaloo, get back here right this
instant.
Those two will never change, will they?
>> Oh, thank God. It was only a nightmare.
>> Scooter, was that you screaming? Are you
having another one of your homosexual
nightmares again?
>> Yeah, but it's nothing ant holiday. Go
back to bed
>> someday, but not today.
>> Trixie. Yeah, this movie sucks major
balls.
>> Okay, the coast is clear. Every pony in
quick.
Celestia is coming. Chrysalis, get out
of here.
Oh, hi sis. You don't have to bother
checking up on us. You know, we aren't
going anywhere. Yeah, well, I felt bad
not letting you have that sleepover that
you wanted, Luna. So, I bought you
something to make up for it.
>> Yeah. What's that?
>> IMAX tickets to a midnight showing of
Scream 7.
>> The limited time only screams seven
popcorn bucket. You bought this for me?
But I don't understand. How did you even
find the money to afford such a
magnificent thing? I used the money I
made from dancing at the club. I know
you didn't want me to keep it since it's
dirty money and all, but I figured that
if I used the money to buy something for
some pony that they really, really want,
it wouldn't be dirty anymore.
Flawless. Something tells me we just
made a worthwhile investment up in this
[__] I feel the sun through my whole
heart.
I hear the wind and it sings for the
ocean.
Ro
Why
don't
you say
just
me
All right, let's give this another go.
Maybe you should try a different color.
You look like a fat ass on lifeguard
duty. I'm embarrassed.
No, don't be. You look amazing. I think
I might be suffering from a hangover
because even though you're standing in
my dirty ass apartment clad in a thong,
and I should be having approximately 17
gay panics right now. I mostly just want
to drink cheap wine and eat Dominoes
Buffalo wings with you while we log on
to the slasher forums and warn the
public about how bad that Scream movie
is. You want to do aggressively normal
couple things? Wow, you must be drunk.
Hey, I didn't say we weren't having sex.
We are absolutely still having sex. I
just want to um appreciate your company
first. Okay.
So, thanks for seeing the movie with me,
I guess. I uh um I I love you, I guess.
Hey, I fainted. You'll have to kiss me
back to life like Snow White.
You're so cringe.
Goodness, you're still here. That means
you watched the whole thing. That makes
you one of the real ones. If you liked
it that much, you might consider
supporting Tamers 12345's Patreon. It
really, really helps Tamers make more
videos. stories take a lot of love and
work, you know, and when people support
him, it makes him super motivated. Only
if you want to, though. No pressure at
all. I'm just happy you stayed to watch
until the very end. Although, you might
find some secret goodies over there.